Come on, Setsu. Say hi to Yuhi-chan.
Hey.
Um, uh...
Want to play with me?
No, thanks.
It's too hot.
What?!
At first, he seemed like
a scary, unfriendly boy.
But because we lived so close,
we spent a lot of time together.
He helped me with school,
played with me, and over time...
As I learned how kind he was, I...
What's wrong?
Would I have to go to a place like this if
I wanted to go to the same high school as you?
L Academy
Free Trial
Available
Just kidding. Let's go home.
I have to help make dinner.
Anul acesta, devino cel mai bun tu.
Study Period
Summer Classes
One-on-one lessons to
tackle your weaknesses!
An environment to
boost motivation!
Two minutes from station exit 2
Hey!
What do you think... about what I said?
Maybe you should aim for an easier school.
We don't have to go to the same
school if it's too much trouble.
You'd just make things harder
for yourself in the long run.
I get it. Never mind.
Hey, Yuhi?
Modern Japanese   Free Phoneme   Verb
Adjective    Adjective Verb    Noun   Adverb
See ya.
Academia L
Engleză
Ascultare
Matematică 1
Matematică 2
Japoneză
I guess I'm not good enough...
Hey, why the gloomy face?
Were your mock exam results bad?
Poor thing. She looks crushed.
Seriously?
If it's beyond your abilities,
just give up. You'll have more fun.
I...
Deep down, you get it, don't you?
Just stop studying and hang out with us.
Come on, let's do it.
Let's play. We know more fun stuff.
Let's let all the stress out, right?
Uh, sorry, guys.
We're busy studying,
so please find someone else to pick on.
Huh?
Yuki-kun...
"Yuki-kun"?
What, she has a guy?
Sorry to bother you.
Damn, what a buzzkill.
Let's go grab something to eat.
Yeah.
Why are you here?
So? What are you going to do?
Huh? What do you mean?
What they said wasn't entirely wrong.
Reaching beyond your
limits won't help anyone.
I...
Even if people tell me I'm not good enough,
I still want to go to the same school as you.
Then there's no other way, I guess.
If that's what you're determined to do,
I'll have to buckle down and pitch in.
Huh?
I'm saying I'll help you study.
But I won't go easy on you, no matter
how much you cry and complain.
Yes, please! Thank you!
I wanted to be with Yuki-kun,
who I love so much, forever...
Episodul 5
Călcându-i pentru a doua oară pe urme
Open fire!
We did it!
It worked!
I know, right?! It's awesome!
Finish!
Yuhi-san, that was impressive.
The others have improved a lot, as well.
We'll call it a day for now.
Good work, everyone.
Thank you!
Good work, guys.
I'm so hungry.
Um, do you have a moment?
You're Yuki-kun's friends from
the last time he was here...
Or rather, his companions, right?
That's right. We still see him
as a friend and a companion.
Setsu-sama tends to draw
others in unconsciously,
so who knows if he feels
the same way about us?
I still have the utmost respect for him,
and wish I could stand by him forever
and gaze at the same scenery with him.
Anyway, what is your question?
C-Can you give me special training?!
I want to be with Yuki-kun, too!
This is the peaceful world
that Setsu-sama created.
And, as we speak, Setsu-sama is surely
fighting somewhere beyond this sky we see
to maintain peace in this world.
As Setsu-sama's companions,
we're staying prepared so we
can act at a moment's notice.
I have both the desire to be with Yuki-kun
and the determination to do what it takes.
But I lack the strength, so...
Elka-san,
please!
Once you've spoken those words to me...
I'll never let you say you were just joking!
Here I come!
It's not over!
You've grown much stronger than you realize.
All of the kids that came from
the other world are exceptional,
but you're quite special, even among them.
But still, if you wish to
stand by Setsu-sama's side,
there is something you definitely lack.
What's the thing that I lack?
This is a sewer infested with monsters.
We sometimes use this as a final
training ground for soldiers.
M-Monsters? Final training?
Here it comes.
Huh?
This is no time to be startled!
Now fight!
Don't flinch! Fight!
You have more than enough strength!
Elka-san!
I did it! I fought!
Don't let your guard down!
Now!
Take this!
H-Haven't you had enough?
You're hurt. If you move now...
Finish it.
You have indeed become stronger.
In terms of magic ability alone,
you're almost equal to me.
But...
This is war.
Kill the enemy, or they
will kill your friends.
The other side thinks the same way.
If you want to protect those dear to you,
you must fight and end lives.
That determination is what you lack.
The determination... to take lives...
Elka-san...
This is what I lack...
Yes, come in!
Hey there. Mind if I come in?
There, that's better.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Elka was crazy to throw you into
a real battle so suddenly.
No, I asked for it.
I see you as one of us, too.
Huh?
We don't know what Setsu was
like in the other world,
but he looks at you the same way he looks at us.
That's also why I understand
where Elka's coming from.
We can't teach determination.
Elka is hard on you because she
wants to treat you as a true equal.
Thea-san...
Why do you want to be with Setsu so badly?
You know being near him will
put you in lots of danger.
Because Yuki-kun has helped
me out my whole life.
So, this time, I want to be the one to help him.
I see.
Well, all we can do is meddle,
but I do wish you good luck.
Thanks!
It'll be all right. Yuhi is strong.
That much is obvious.
Defending herself on the battlefield
should be easy for her at this point.
But if she fights alongside us,
who knows what kind of dangerous
foes she'll eventually face?
And you don't think Setsu wants us to
force that kind of determination on Yuhi?
But that's not for us to decide,
and not for Setsu to decide, either.
It's all up to Yuhi herself.
All we can do is respect the determination
that Yuhi finds for herself.
I'll sleep a bit more.
Goodnight.
I...
Excuse me.
Is this about last night?
Glein-san...
Being hesitant about taking lives is natural.
Even if it's for the sake
of someone precious to you.
Glein-san, how did you gather
the determination to fight?
I just chose to make others suffer,
rather than watch the
people around me suffer.
Like any other soldier.
But that's just what works for me.
You have your own determination.
You have to find the answer by yourself.
My...
determination...
Setsu-san probably wants you to come up
with the answer that best suits you.
I want to stay true to myself,
yet I want to fight...
Since you've returned,
does that mean you've
found your determination?
Yes. I've made my decision.
Forcing yourself out of your
comfort zone in battle might break you.
Elka-san, please witness my determination.
Impressive.
Outstanding power and accuracy alike.
Yuhi-san, I'll admit, your determination is—
No.
It's not dead.
I just temporarily incapacitated it.
This is my determination:
to never take a life.
I will never lose, and I will
never take anyone's life!
Yuhi-san...
Well, you got me. That answer
is just like Setsu-sama's.
I'm impressed by your determination,
but that would require an astounding
amount of power to pull off.
Yes! I'll become much, much stronger!
So that I can protect Elka-san, Yuki-kun,
and everyone else.
The king has issued his decree.
We, the Knights of Distinia, in order
to protect our nation and its citizens,
will leave tomorrow at dawn for
the demonic nation of Eviltheon.
Everyone, prepare yourselves,
both physically and mentally!
Sunteți liberi!
So the time is finally here...
I have to fight. I don't wanna die...
Can I really shoot a person?
Can we really fight,
after such brief training?
Așteaptă doar, Yuki.
Data viitoare
Maestru și ucenic pentru a doua oară
Data viitoare: Maestru și
ucenic pentru a doua oară.